Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: CWA Officers' Papers, 1939-1990
  - Subseries V:E: Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1947-1987
    - Retirement Dinner (#2): W.A. Smallwood, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Retirement Dinner (#3): W.A. Smallwood, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Retirement Dinner (#4): W.A. Smallwood, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Labor Management: 2s/DOL Audit, 1948-1972 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Labor Management: DOL Audit, 1973-1975 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Labor Management: 2s Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Financial Reports: Irregularities, 1960-1972 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Financial Correspondence: Forged Checks, 1968, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Financial Correspondence: Dist. 4, Local 4389, 1982-1984 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Financial Correspondence: Dist. 4, Local 4389, 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Hughes Trial (District 4), 1987 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: New CWA Building, 1970-1976 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Wand & Hall Assoc., 1972-1977 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Construction Correspondence: Extra Annex Cost, 1973, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Officers Correspondence: Credit Unions, 1948-1951, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Officers Correspondence: Initiation Fees, 1947-1949 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Officers Correspondence: Delinquencies and Waiving of Dues, 1947 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Officers Correspondence: Payroll Deduction of Dues Recognition, Maintenance of Membership, 1947-1949 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Officers Correspondence: Disposition of Dues, 1947-1948 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Officers Correspondence: Dues Deductions, Cash Collections, Suspended Members, Part-Time Members, 1951-1955 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - NFTW and CWA Dues and Assessments History: 1939-1951, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Merrimack Valley Works: Negotiations and Strike, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - CWA & North Carolina Works Strike, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Union Proposals: Part One, 1957-1961 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Union Proposals: Part Two, 1957-1961 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Union Proposals: Part Three, 1957-1961 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Job Content Study: Wage Survey, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Job Content Study: Vols. 1 and 2, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - New York Tele. Com. Bargaining: Part 1, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - New York Tele. Com. Bargaining: Part 2, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Arbitration bet/ New York Tel. Co. And CWA, 1961-1962 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - CWA and AT&T Negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - CWA and AT&T Negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, Jul 20, 1970-Jul 22, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, Jul 23, 1970-Jul 24, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, Jul 27, 1970-Jul 29, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, Aug 24, 1970-Aug 26, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - CWA Structure Review Committee, Nov 4, 1970-Nov 6, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Structure Review Committee: " Priorities of the Seventies", 1970 (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Summary of the Outlook for the Economy and the Bell System, Part One, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Summary of the Outlook for the Economy and the Bell System, Part Two, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 28)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Meeting, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 29)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Meeting, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 30)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Meeting Reports and Notes, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 31)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: 1971 Part One (Box 87, Folder 32)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: 1971 Part Two (Box 87, Folder 33)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: 1971 Part Three (Box 87, Folder 34)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Summary Papers and Proposals, Part One, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Summary Papers and Proposals, Part Two, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Summary Papers and Proposals, Part Three, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements, Part One, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements, Part Two, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements, Part three, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements, Part Four, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - CWA and AT&T Negotiations, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council, Sep 13, 1972-Sep 14, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council, Sep 13, 1972-Sep 14, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Bell System Collective Bargaining Primer for 1974, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - United Farm Workers Relief Fund: Letter from Cesar Chavez, 1973-1974 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Part One, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Part Two, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Bell System Bargaining Council: Part Three, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining Primer: pp. 1-150, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining Primer: pp. 151-300, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining Primer: pp. 301-450, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Collective Bargaining Primer: pp. 451-524, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - CWA and AT&T: Negotiations, Part One, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - CWA and AT&T: Negotiations, Part Two, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - CWA and AT&T: Negotiations, Part Three, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - CWA and AT&T: Negotiations, Part Four, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Telephone Systems (General): Bargaining Council, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - External Organizing: CWA Contract Analysis, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - External Organizing: CWA Contract Analysis, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - External Organizing:"Organization Development Seminar" Transcript, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Dues Rate Study Committee, Part One, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Dues Rate Study Committee, Part Two, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Dues Rate Study Committee, Part Three, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Dues Rate Study Committee, Part Four, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Bell System Bargaining 1977, Part One (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Bell System Bargaining 1977, Part Two (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Bell System Bargaining 1977, Part Three (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - AT&T Statements on Negotiations: Responses, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - CWA and Bell System: Negotiations, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - CWA and Bell System: Negotiations, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - New Dues Structure, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Dues Structure Report, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Dues Structure Report, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - CWA One Million Dollar Pledge for Mine Worker Relief, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Dues Implementation: Correspondence; Weekly Summary for District One, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Dues Implementation: Districts Two and Three, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Dues Implementation: Districts Four and Five, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Dues Implementation: Districts Six, Seven and Eight, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Dues Implementation: Districts Nine, Ten, and Eleven, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Dues Implementation: Districts Twelve Correspondence, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Local Dues Vote Report: Districts One to Six, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Local Dues Vote Report: Districts Seven to Twelve, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part One, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Two, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Three, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Four, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Five, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Six, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - One-Year Dues Projections: Part Seven, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - CWA Wage Differentials Study, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Bell System Bargaining, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Bell System Bargaining, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Bargaining Items Analysis: pp. 1-180, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Bargaining Items Analysis: pp. 181-289, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - National Training Fund Meeting, Feb 9, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - National Training Fund Meeting, Feb 9, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - CWA Merger Agreement: Fed. Of Tel. Workers, PA, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Proposed Restructure of CWA, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Line of Business Waiver Requests: Judge Greene's Opinion, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - CWA/QWL Staff Union Meeting, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Quality of Work Life, 1984-1986 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Elva's Defense Fund Bible: Part One, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Elva's Defense Fund Bible: Part Two, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Elva's Defense Fund Bible: Part Three, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Elva's Defense Fund Bible: Part Four, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Elva's Defense Fund Bible: Part Five, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - United System Bargaining Council: Proposals for Consideration, pp. 1-180, Jun 3, 1987-Jun 5, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - United System Bargaining Council: Proposals for Consideration, pp. 181-298, Jun 3, 1987-Jun 5, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - United System Bargaining Council: Proposals for Consideration, pp. 299-325, Jun 3, 1987-Jun 5, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Financial Correspondence, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Dues Increase: Convention Action, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Dues Increase: Convention Action, Continued, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Dues Increas: Survey, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - CWA Dues Authorization: Canada, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Report of Dues Processing, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Percentage Dues, 1964-1969 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Maintenance of Dues: Policy Procedure, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Maintenance of Dues, 1967, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Dues: Cash Collection, Local 6396, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Dues Increase Charts: 1959-1970 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - CWA Convention: Dues, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Percentage Dues, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee: Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Membership & Dues Cards, 1975-1978 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Series VI: CWA Bargaining/Negotiations, 1947-1983
  This series primarily consists of records from the Office of the President (Joseph A. Beirne and Glenn E. Watts). These include bargaining books and reports, Bargaining Council papers, Negotiating Committee records, letters to members, materials relating to pattern bargaining, files concerning benefit matters, minutes of bargaining conferences, collective bargaining agreements, contract reviews, records documenting long-lines bargaining, negotiations at Western Electric, and grievances.
  - Administrative Bargaining Letters: Joseph A. Beirne, 1957-1959 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Bargaining Letters: Joseph A. Beirne, 1960-1965 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Bargaining Letters: Joseph A. Beirne, 1966-1970 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Bargaining Letters: Joseph A. Beirne, 1971-1982 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining Notes: Joseph A. Beirne, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining Book Material: General Index, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 1 & 2, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 3 & 4, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 5 & 6, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 7-9, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 10-15, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 16-22, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining Book Material: Sections 23-30, 1956-1961 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Joseph A. Beirne- Members- All Bargaining Councils, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Collective Bargaining Policy Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining Policy Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Negotiations: Knecht, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining Committee: Joseph A. Beirne, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - General System Bargaining Council, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Telephone Systems Bargaining Council: Joseph A. Beirne, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: First Meeting, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Bell System Bargaining Meeting: Glenn E. Watts, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: Glenn E. Watts, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements 1-22: Joseph A. Beirne, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: Statements 23-50, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Final Bargaining Reports: Districts 1-6, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Final Bargaining Reports: Districts 7-10, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - General Systems Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, Oct 18, 1971-Oct 19, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - General Systems Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, Mar 15, 1971-Mar 16, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining Book: Joseph A. Beirne, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: Speeches 1-20: Joseph A. Beirne, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council: Speeches 21-50, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, Sep 13, 1972-Sep 14, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, Nov 12, 1973-Nov 14, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, Jan 16, 1974-Jan 17, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council Meeting: Joseph A. Beirne, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Bell System Bargaining Council Primer: Glenn E. Watts, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - General Telephone Systems Bargaining Council, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - General Telephone Systems Bargaining Council, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - General Telephone Systems Bargaining Council, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - General Telephone Systems Bargaining Council, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - United System Bargaining Council, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Bell System Strike Manual: G.E. Watts, undated (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Information Letters, 1961-1966 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Information Letters, 1966-1973 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - CBPC/BSBC: ATT & RBOC Resolutions, 1958-1986 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - CWA News: Bargaining Newspapers & Notes, 1958, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - CWA Bargaining Materials, 1949-1986 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - CWA Bargaining Materials, 1957-1964 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - CWA Bargaining Materials, 1966-1970 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - CWA Bargaining Materials, 1962-1971 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Negotiating Committees Activities, 1947-1949 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Chief Negotiators Meeting, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Civic Leaders, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining Demands, 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Division 45: Proceedings; Joseph A. Beirne Speech, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - National Planning, 1948-1950 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - National Planning Bargaining School, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - National Planning: Contract Approval, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - National Planning: Reopening on Wages, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - National Planning: Executive Board Poll, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - National Planning: President's Negotiating Conference, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Proceedings of President's Conference, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - National Planning, 1952-1953 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - National Planning: Notices to Bargain and Dispute, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - National Planning: Notices to Bargain and Dispute, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - National Planning: Notices to Bargain and Dispute, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - National Planning: Notices to Bargain and Dispute, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - National Planning, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - National Planning, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Ind. & Southwestern Bell Strikes: Relief for Suspended Member, 1953-1955 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - CWA Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining, 1955-1957 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Program Study Committee, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Executive Board Meeting, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Notices of Dispute and Contract Negotiations, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Minutes of Executive Board Meeting, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - National Planning: Notices of Dispute & Contract Negotiations, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Lawsuit Against Ohio Bell, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Notices to Bargain and Notices of Dispute, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: W.E. Sales, Installation, Manufacturing, Bell Labs, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Correspondence with AT&T & Bell Companies, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Correspondence, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining: Bell System Proposal on Revision of Progression Schedules, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining, 1957-1964 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining: All Districts, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Bargaining, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Bargaining, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Bargaining, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Bargaining, 1967-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: Letters to Members, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining, 1967-1968 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining, 1968-1970 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Pattern Bargaining, 1964-1971 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Proposals, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Bell System and Memos of Agreements, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: 100 Million Dollar Defense Fund, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Changes in Bargaining, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Union Proposals, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining: Economic, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining: Closing of Bargaining, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining: Compulsory Arbitration, 1946-1948 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: Arbitration, Uniform Arbitration Act, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining: Area Differentials, 1953-1956 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Area Differentials, Big City Problem, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Automation, 1946-1952 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Automation: Diebold Study, 1964-1965 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Automation, 1953-1955 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Automation, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining Council: NYC Meeting, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Automation, Governor's Conference, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Automation, "Report on Technology & Manpower in the Telephone Industry", 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining Council, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Automation, Speeches, 1955-1966 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining Committees: Size, 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining Committees: Size, 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining Committees: Rates of Pay, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining Committees: Rules, Size, Salary, 1953-1955 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining Committees: Size, 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining: Bell System Propaganda, 1947-1953 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining: Bell System Savings Plan, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining: Bell System Hiring Practices, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining: Bell System, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining: Bell System Savings Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining: Contracts Clauses, Duration, and Termination, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining: Contracts, 1947-1972 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining: Concentrated Employment Program, 1967-1970 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Bargaining: Compensation, Overtime Pay, and Merit Increases, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Bargaining: Compensation and Overtime, 1968-1971 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Bargaining: Federal Labor Management Conference, 1949-1972 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Bargaining: Foreign Equipment, 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: Foreign Equipment; Carterfone Decision, 1970-1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining: Grievances, 1943-1966 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Group Life Insurance, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Group Life Insurance, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Group Life Insurance, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Group Life Insurance, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Health Insurance, 1949-1966 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Policy Committee, 1950-1958 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, Descriptions, Classifications; Traffic Patrol Operator, Indiana Bell, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, 1956-1958 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining: Job Titles, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining: Labor Grading Committee Appointment, 1952-1953 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Loyalty Oaths & Security, 1951-1955 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining: Loyalty Oaths & Security, 1955-1957 (Box 101, Folder 18)